{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072359447","data":{"timestamp":" 948072359446"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072367979","data":{"timestamp":" 948072367978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072371925","data":{"timestamp":" 948072371924"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072376084","data":{"timestamp":" 948072376084"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072381088","data":{"timestamp":" 948072381088"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072386738","data":{"timestamp":" 948072386738"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072392682","data":{"timestamp":" 948072392681"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072405206","data":{"timestamp":" 948072405206"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072417050","data":{"timestamp":" 948072417049"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072422174","data":{"timestamp":" 948072422174"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072429531","data":{"timestamp":" 948072429531"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072436013","data":{"timestamp":" 948072436013"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072439797","data":{"timestamp":" 948072439797"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072445383","data":{"timestamp":" 948072445383"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072451539","data":{"timestamp":" 948072451539"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072457252","data":{"timestamp":" 948072457251"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072462896","data":{"timestamp":" 948072462896"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072468548","data":{"timestamp":" 948072468548"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072472409","data":{"timestamp":" 948072472409"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072475948","data":{"timestamp":" 948072475947"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 3de3218d-0017-461d-b30e-c781190858d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072488819","data":{"timestamp":" 948072488819"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072489042","data":{"timestamp":" 948072489042"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072490017","data":{"timestamp":" 948072490016"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072491296","data":{"timestamp":" 948072491296"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072494201","data":{"timestamp":" 948072494201"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072495044","data":{"timestamp":" 948072495043"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072495359","data":{"timestamp":" 948072495359"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072496601","data":{"timestamp":" 948072496600"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072500211","data":{"timestamp":" 948072500211"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072501195","data":{"timestamp":" 948072501195"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072501448","data":{"timestamp":" 948072501448"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072502391","data":{"timestamp":" 948072502391"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072505301","data":{"timestamp":" 948072505300"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072506338","data":{"timestamp":" 948072506338"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072506817","data":{"timestamp":" 948072506816"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072511348","data":{"timestamp":" 948072511346"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072511456","data":{"timestamp":" 948072511456"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" d64d6bdd-0033-4bd1-b246-ca8e781d9709"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072521831","data":{"timestamp":" 948072521830"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 94775708-1004-480e-8cac-92dbe744df91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072521964","data":{"timestamp":" 948072521964"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 94775708-1004-480e-8cac-92dbe744df91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072522037","data":{"timestamp":" 948072522037"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 94775708-1004-480e-8cac-92dbe744df91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072535684","data":{"timestamp":" 948072535683"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 94775708-1004-480e-8cac-92dbe744df91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072546065","data":{"timestamp":" 948072546065"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 94775708-1004-480e-8cac-92dbe744df91"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072555325","data":{"timestamp":" 948072555325"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072555554","data":{"timestamp":" 948072555553"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072556531","data":{"timestamp":" 948072556530"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072557807","data":{"timestamp":" 948072557806"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072560711","data":{"timestamp":" 948072560710"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072561582","data":{"timestamp":" 948072561581"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072561941","data":{"timestamp":" 948072561941"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072563189","data":{"timestamp":" 948072563188"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072566683","data":{"timestamp":" 948072566683"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072567666","data":{"timestamp":" 948072567666"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072567920","data":{"timestamp":" 948072567920"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072568864","data":{"timestamp":" 948072568864"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072571695","data":{"timestamp":" 948072571695"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072572728","data":{"timestamp":" 948072572728"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072573201","data":{"timestamp":" 948072573201"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072577728","data":{"timestamp":" 948072577727"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072577843","data":{"timestamp":" 948072577843"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" ff4d0d75-057a-42cb-91a4-a6598cbfd92b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072590832","data":{"timestamp":" 948072590832"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" NYAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072594386","data":{"timestamp":" 948072594386"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072595975","data":{"timestamp":" 948072595975"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072599293","data":{"timestamp":" 948072599292"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072600881","data":{"timestamp":" 948072600881"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072605451","data":{"timestamp":" 948072605451"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072607011","data":{"timestamp":" 948072607011"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" NYATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072610751","data":{"timestamp":" 948072610751"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072612343","data":{"timestamp":" 948072612343"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndevu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" NDEVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072615339","data":{"timestamp":" 948072615339"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndevu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEVU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072616915","data":{"timestamp":" 948072616914"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANASI"," userResponse":" NANASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072620463","data":{"timestamp":" 948072620463"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-N.rand.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072621868","data":{"timestamp":" 948072621867"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nanasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072621961","data":{"timestamp":" 948072621961"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nanasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072632783","data":{"timestamp":" 948072632783"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nanasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:N..N.all.rand.all.stat.show.104","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072641429","data":{"timestamp":" 948072641429"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9daddfd3-2dd3-4702-9939-c64ef5a999e8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-N.rand.53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nanasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072650204","data":{"timestamp":" 948072650204"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9739169d-4a29-4a01-b1a9-75e5a2cec706"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072650423","data":{"timestamp":" 948072650423"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9739169d-4a29-4a01-b1a9-75e5a2cec706"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072650499","data":{"timestamp":" 948072650499"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 9739169d-4a29-4a01-b1a9-75e5a2cec706"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072660754","data":{"timestamp":" 948072660754"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072661140","data":{"timestamp":" 948072661140"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072661633","data":{"timestamp":" 948072661632"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072661983","data":{"timestamp":" 948072661983"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072662396","data":{"timestamp":" 948072662395"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072662877","data":{"timestamp":" 948072662877"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072663105","data":{"timestamp":" 948072663105"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072666340","data":{"timestamp":" 948072666339"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072666378","data":{"timestamp":" 948072666377"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072667100","data":{"timestamp":" 948072667100"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072667500","data":{"timestamp":" 948072667500"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072667797","data":{"timestamp":" 948072667796"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072668011","data":{"timestamp":" 948072668011"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072668211","data":{"timestamp":" 948072668210"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072668535","data":{"timestamp":" 948072668535"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072668768","data":{"timestamp":" 948072668767"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072672029","data":{"timestamp":" 948072672022"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072672447","data":{"timestamp":" 948072672447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072674994","data":{"timestamp":" 948072674993"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072675203","data":{"timestamp":" 948072675203"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072675415","data":{"timestamp":" 948072675414"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072678979","data":{"timestamp":" 948072678978"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072682644","data":{"timestamp":" 948072682644"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072683668","data":{"timestamp":" 948072683668"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072686318","data":{"timestamp":" 948072686318"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072686691","data":{"timestamp":" 948072686691"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072687174","data":{"timestamp":" 948072687174"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072687517","data":{"timestamp":" 948072687517"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072687920","data":{"timestamp":" 948072687920"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072688393","data":{"timestamp":" 948072688393"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072688617","data":{"timestamp":" 948072688617"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072691811","data":{"timestamp":" 948072691811"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072691846","data":{"timestamp":" 948072691845"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072692559","data":{"timestamp":" 948072692559"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072692953","data":{"timestamp":" 948072692953"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072693247","data":{"timestamp":" 948072693247"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072693451","data":{"timestamp":" 948072693450"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072693644","data":{"timestamp":" 948072693644"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072693958","data":{"timestamp":" 948072693958"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072694182","data":{"timestamp":" 948072694182"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072696854","data":{"timestamp":" 948072696854"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072696925","data":{"timestamp":" 948072696925"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072711343","data":{"timestamp":" 948072711342"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" e54c940e-6924-4e3a-a46d-e4c4116dc8be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072734547","data":{"timestamp":" 948072734547"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_m_s"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072741236","data":{"timestamp":" 948072741236"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_n_r"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072747861","data":{"timestamp":" 948072747860"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_n_g"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072755340","data":{"timestamp":" 948072755340"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_n_g"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072765697","data":{"timestamp":" 948072765697"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_n_g"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072771897","data":{"timestamp":" 948072771897"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_n_g"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072778526","data":{"timestamp":" 948072778526"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_n_l"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072786004","data":{"timestamp":" 948072786004"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_n_l"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072792664","data":{"timestamp":" 948072792664"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_f_w"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072800109","data":{"timestamp":" 948072800109"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_f_w"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072806773","data":{"timestamp":" 948072806773"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_n_j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072814253","data":{"timestamp":" 948072814253"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_n_j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:N..N.all.10.rand.say.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072814397","data":{"timestamp":" 948072814397"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_o_n_j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072820308","data":{"timestamp":" 948072820308"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042547"," gameId":" 8288244c-1e11-4746-bb74-eda1fd1f0086"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_N..N.all.10.rand.say.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_o_n_j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}